Herwindo Artono

<u>herwindo.artono@gmail.com</u> | +628122013050 | Jl. Remaja No.20, Jati Pulogadung, Jakarta Timur Website | Github | Stackoverflow | Treehouse | freecodecamp | Portfolio

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Front-end Developer with 3+ years of professional experience designing, developing and managing complex Web and mobile Application. Specializes in Vue js and responsive design. Unique combined technical and managerial expertise with 7+ years experience in managing people, this add a plus when designing user interface and user experience for an application.

TECHNICAL EXPERTISE:

Javascript

Vue

Firebase

Adobe XD

HTML / HTML 5

React

Node js

Adobe Photoshop

CSS / CSS3 / SCSS

noSQL

REST API

Django

Bootstrap

rethinkdb

Socket IO

Flutter

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Frontend Developer • Dec 2018 - present

PT. Aplikasi Karya Anak Bangsa (Gojek)

- Implement concept, methodology and development workflow for faster development time. Working it together with team, building new site Gojek's new Brand.
- Lead frontend development for various project: GoLucky, GoFigure, Ramadhan, GoPlay.
- Front End Engineer / Product Owner 2017 2018

PT. T&E Simulation, Project Management Application

- In 3 months, succeeded build a working attendance system to measure 32+ employees performance, that consist of web (SPA), mobile application, telegram bots, and AWS service.
- After product implementation, the team showed rough improvement in productivity by delivering a 12 month project in only 9 month (25% faster), the fastest project delivery in company.
- Full Stack Engineer 2015 2017

PT. T&E Simulation, Wargaming Simulation Project

- Built 7 from total 26 Application (27%) to deliver in a year using Vue JS, socket.io, Node js, Express, Rethinkdb and Mongodb.
- Built 3 of 4 mobile application with API server in 3 month, this application intended to be installed in 50+ iPad using framework7, Vue, PWA, node is and socket.io.
- Lead front end engineering for a browser based application that serve prestigious training for national airforce. This Training held 4 to 5 times a year.
- Working in a team of 8 developers, Assisting the lead developer in standup meetings, git and kanban agile implementation.

MANAGERIAL WORK EXPERIENCE

Operations Manager • 2017 - 2018

PT. T&E Simulation

- Managing resources to meet each projects demands.
- Working with in house developer, building company's project management system application.
- Project Management Officer 2012 2015

PT. T&E Simulation, various simulator project

- Supporting Project Managers, operating their projects.
- Setup Project management, Finance and Procurement system using Atlassian JIRA and Confluence, and also Trello, so that 3 projects with around 70+ employee have one single source of information they can access on site or at the office.
- Lead 20 person to do daily Test Dispatch Order for every day in 3 month on project's final product.
 Resulting a 3 years long project can be accepted by client in final crucial testing, Site Acceptance test.
- Documenting software & configuration versions.

EDUCATION

Master of Business Administration • 2009 - 2012

Bandung Institute of Technology

Majoring in entrepreneurship, GPA: 3.45

- Bachelor of Economy • 2000 - 2005

Padjadjaran University

Majoring in Marketing Management, GPA: 3.04

NON FORMAL EDUCATION

Front-end and Full Stack Development • 2018
 Freecodecamp

- Web App Development · 2015 - 2016

Envato Tutsplus Premium, codeschools, treehouse

CERTIFICATIONS & ACHIEVEMENTS

- Completing 900 hours of freecodecamp represented coursework in roughly 320 hrs (2.8x faster)
 - Javascript Algorithms and Data Structure Certification 2018
 - API and Microservices Certification 2018
 - Responsive Web Design Certification 2018
- Winning design contest for banner ads 2018